All right, Mrs. Freemantle,
we will see you next week.
Oh, thank you, Dr. Harper.
And remember, no more rough sex.
Ha, ha.
Dr. Harper, you're terrible.
Okay, bye-bye.
I wish I was kidding.
The woman's a freak.
You are so good with the patients,
Dr. Harper.
Well, thank you.
You're warm and personable
and funny, ha, ha.
Oh, I'm all right, ha, ha.
But you, the patients love you.
- Heh. No.
- Ah, don't give me "no."
- I'm giving you "no."
- Well, I'm not taking "no."
- Don't make me blush.
- I'm making you blush.
Well, I'm blushing.
- So we all done for the day?
- Yeppers.
Mrs. Freemantle
was our last patient.
Okay, then, uh, I will see
your smiling face tomorrow. Ha, ha.
Well, it's only smiling
because it's looking at you.
- Don't make me blush.
- I'm making you blush.
Well, I'm blushing. Ha, ha.
I'm so sorry.
- I- I should apologize.
- I'm the one who stepped over the line.
- No, I stepped too.
- No, I stepped first.
- No, no-
- Don't give me "no, no."
I'm giving you "no, no."
- We can't do this.
- I'm sorry, I can't help it.
I ache for you.
Yeah, well, I'm not
all that comfortable right now either.
- It's- It's just that I-
- No, you don't have to explain.
I understand.
Okay.
Okay, well, then, uh,
I guess I will see you tomorrow.
I'll be here at, uh, 7:30.
In case you wanna get in early.
Oh, okay.
Uh, I might actually wanna get in early.
You're the boss.
You can get in anytime you want.
Oh, God.
- Hi.
- Hey.
Mind if I watch the game?
Uh, actually, I came in here
for a little quiet time.
Huh.
Still quieter than sleeping
under the Santa Monica Pier.
- I'm conflicted, Charlie.
- Shh, quiet time.
Do you think you can choose
who you love?
Oh, boy.
What's his name?
What-? No.
All right.
Come out when you're ready.
Do you remember my receptionist?
The itsy-bitsy spider
who climbed up my waterspout?
Yeah, whatever happened to her?
You dumped her
after one depraved weekend.
And I had to give her a raise,
health insurance...
...and a paid vacation
to keep her from quitting.
Oh, good, thanks
for smoothing that over for me.
Hey, you think she has plans
for this weekend?
What is wrong with you?
Uh, I am trying to tell you that
I am starting to have feelings for her.
For who?
- For Melissa.
- Who's Melissa?
My receptionist.
Oh...
So I should forget
about this weekend?
Yes, you should forget
about this weekend!
I was just asking,
you don't have to bite my head off.
So you and her are, uh...?
Oh, no, no, no,
nothing's happened yet.
Just a little kissing,
and she could feel my enthusiasm.
What are you, NoëI Coward?
Just say "boner."
Why do I bother talking to you?
Beats the hell out of me.
The thing is, uh,
Melissa and I have this chemistry...
...and it's really hard not to act on it.
Yeah. It's tough
when you work together.
Right.
- You don't crap where you eat.
- I know.
You don't dip your pen
in company ink.
And you never bang a woman
who owns a snake or a bird.
- What?
- They're usually nuts.
So, what you're faced with here
is a moral dilemma.
Ah, I'll say.
Whether or not to have a relationship
with your employee.
Exactly.
- I got it, I got it.
- Oh, you do?
Fire her, then boink her.
I don't got it?
You don't got it.
I'm right about the snakes
and birds though.
Really? The one who works for him?
- Yep.
- Tinker Bell with the knockers?
The same.
Well, everybody makes
that mistake once.
I crossed that line in the '70s...
...when I was cleaning house
for Mr. Telly Savalas.
- No kidding, TV's Kojak?
- One and the same.
- What happened?
- What do you think happened?
He's Greek, a man of passion.
You can't tie your shoes
around those guys.
- That's rough.
- Bet your ass, it's rough.
- Morning.
CHARLIE: Morning.
So, Zippy, I hear you've been sinking
your putts on the company golf course.
Thanks for telling her.
Thanks for telling me.
Word of advice:
It may seem like fun and games
at the beginning...
...but mark my words,
sooner or later you're gonna wake up...
...with a broken heart
and a lollipop stuck to your keister.
You wanna explain that to me?
I'd rather forget I ever heard it.
So decided what you're gonna do
about Melissa?
Oh, there's nothing to do. Just have to take
the physical feelings I have for her...
...and channel them into something
creative, productive...
...something that'll last.
You're gonna have sex with
the vacuum cleaner again, aren't you?
That wasn't sex,
that was an accident.
Once is an accident.
- Morning, Melissa.
- Good morning, Dr. Harper.
How's my schedule look today?
It's packed pretty tight.
Oh, okay. Uh, tight's good.
You know, better tight than, uh...
You know...
Thank God for scoliosis, ha, ha.
Um...
Listen, Melissa, um,
about what happened yesterday-
Please, you don't have
to say anything.
Yes, yes I do.
We obviously have feelings
for each other.
There's nothing wrong with that.
It's a beautiful thing. It's- It's natural.
But for us to maintain a working
relationship and, I hope, friendship...
...I think it would be unwise
to succumb to those feelings.
I agree.
Oh, good. Good. I'm glad, ha, ha.
Oh, well-
Now we got that out of the way.
Uh, what time does
my packed schedule begin?
Uh, not for a half-hour.
Half-hour?
Yeppers.
Nothing for a half-hour?
Wide open.
Everything work out at the office?
Uh-huh.
Managed to keep your hands off
Really Little Annie Fanny?
Well, not exactly.
But, uh, we did keep it above the waist.
Her waist or yours?
Both. And it wasn't easy.
I haven't checked, but I'm pretty sure...
...my balls look like two-thirds
of the Blue Man Group.
Berta, hide the vacuum cleaner!
For the last time,
I use it to get lint off my trousers.
Then why do you call it Brenda?
So when the mood strikes and she's ready...
...you'll be ready too.
Ready today, ready tonight,
ready tomorrow.
I'm ready now.
What's he ready for?
If I were to guess, I'd say he's ready
to screw up his life a little more.
Is that even possible?
We'll see.
I'm hungry.
- So eat something.
- There's nothing here I like.
Welcome to my world.
Why are we eating here?
If I have to watch you stuff your face,
I'm gonna need a drink.
- Am I even allowed to be in a bar?
- Probably not.
So if anybody asks,
you're a homely lesbian.
Why do I have to be homely?
Just sit down.
What's that smell?
Stale beer, vomit, urine.
You hungry?
- Hey, Charlie.
- Oh, hey, Janine.
- This is my nephew, Jake.
- Hey, Jake.
How old are you, sweetheart?
Keep your hands off him, Janine.
He's married.
I thought I was a lesbian.
We're just gonna have a couple
of hamburgers, a basket of fries.
He'll have soda, I'll have a draft.
That's not a very healthy dinner
for a growing boy.
Oh, don't worry,
he can process anything.
The other day he ate a handful
of packing peanuts.
You bet me 10 bucks I wouldn't.
Oh, Charlie, shame on you.
Yeah, shame on you.
Tell you what, Jake.
I get out of here in 10 minutes.
Get your uncle
to bring you to my place.
I'll cook you a nice, healthy dinner.
Thanks, but I'm already healthy.
I'll have a hamburger.
No, you won't. We'll be there.
- I don't get a vote?
- You're lucky you're getting dinner.
- Thanks, Janine.
- You're welcome.
What is wrong with you?
Turning that down?
Excuse me, but we have no idea
what kind of cook she is.
Oh, God.
For all we know, she's a vegetarian.
- Dr. Harper, what are you doing here?
- What do you think I'm doing here?
Please don't make me guess.
I'm making you guess.
Correct.
Melissa, honey, who's here?
Uh, Mom, this is my boss, Dr. Harper.
Dr. Harper, this is my mother.
Hello.
Hello, yourself.
I understand there's been some
inappropriate behavior...
...in the workplace.
Oh. Yeah, well, uh, about that.
I just want you to know that I have
nothing but respect your daughter.
- And I would never do anything to-
- I'm just yanking your chain.
Ain't nothing wrong
with bedding the boss.
That's how I wound up
with the little princess here.
And half of Black Angus franchise.
Well, come on in,
I'm watching Hellboy.
- Okay. Thanks.
Hmm...
You smoke dope?
- This is, like, the best dinner ever.
- I'm glad you liked it, Jake.
- You are a great cook.
- And you are a cutie pie.
Oh, I could just eat you up.
- You want another root beer?
- Sure.
Coming right up.
Listen, buddy, you're gonna
have to make yourself scarce.
Maybe take a cab home.
You take a cab home.
I'm doing great.
- How do you figure?
- You blind?
First base on the top of my head,
second base in my ear.
Listen, knucklehead. That woman's
gotta be 10 years older than you.
So? You're like,
15 years older than her.
Step aside, grandpa.
Okay, fun time's over.
- Go wait in the car.
- You go wait in the car.
- No, you go.
How about I put ice cream
in that root beer and make it a float?
Thank you, that'd be great.
It's like she can read my mind.
Go get in the car.
Fine, I'll just go tell Janine you want me
to wait in the car by myself...
...so you can try
and have sex with her.
Sit down, you little bastard.
Now, this picture here
is toward the end of my labor.
That's my vagina...
...and that's Melissa's little head
poking out of me like a groundhog.
Mm.
Hey, I guess if she'd seen her shadow,
I would've had six more weeks of labor.
- It's funny.
- Ha, ha.
You know, of all my kids,
she was the easiest.
Just like popping out
a Ping-Pong ball. Ha, ha.
- That's quite an image.
- Yeah.
Oh, and it was a natural
childbirth too.
No drugs, just a couple peyote buttons
and biting down on a rope.
Mom, would you mind if Dr. Harper
and I have a little time alone?
I'm sorry, honey.
You kids must be as horny
as a couple of drunken rabbits.
Enjoy.
Oh, and, uh, Kama Sutra's
on the bookshelf...
...in case you feel
like pushing the envelope.
I'm sorry about that.
Mom never really made it home
from Woodstock.
Don't be silly. She's delightful.
I'm just gonna close this up now.
Don't mind me.
I'm just gonna roll a fatty
in the backyard...
...and zone out in the hammock.
- Ah, that hit the spot.
- I'm glad you liked it.
The best part of a root beer float:
Your burps taste good.
Listen, Janine,
thanks for everything...
...but I should probably
get this little guy home and come back.
It's way past his bedtime.
What are you talking about?
It's not past my bedtime.
What do you wanna bet he falls asleep
in the car and I have to carry him in?
What do you wanna bet he has
to take a laxative...
...because he's too old
to poop normal?
- All right, that's it.
- Not in the face! Not in the face!
What? Stop that. He's kidding.
I never hit him. Tell her you're kidding.
I'm kidding about that,
but he can be verbally abusive.
- Not funny, Jake.
- The liquor makes him mean.
Okay, I didn't wanna have to do this,
but I am calling your father.
Let him deal with you.
I'm gonna go straighten up
in the kitchen.
You don't know
who you're messing with.
Are you kidding?
I think she's gorgeous!
Ow! Ow!
You don't know
who you're messing with.
Oh, I'm sorry. Uh, hang on.
Charlie, now is not a good time.
All right, put him on.
I can't talk now, Dad. I'm about
to get lucky with an older woman.
What? Where are you?
Jake? Jake?
Alan...
...would you be totally weirded out
by a little mother-daughter tag team?
Hope you're happy.
I hope you're happy.
Could have been happy.
Are you gonna tell me
what happened tonight?
You don't wanna know.
Where you going?
I'm a 14-year-old boy
who recently got ear-boob.
Where do you think I'm going?
Ear-boob?
You don't wanna know.
- So how'd it go with Melissa?
- You don't wanna know.
Oh, come on.
All right. I met her mom,
saw a photo of mom's vagina...
...and chose to leave before
being introduced to the real thing.
You're right, I didn't wanna know.
- Where are you going?
- I'm a 40-year-old guy who recently-
Ah, screw it.
I'm gonna go play with myself.
Hey, that I didn't wanna know.
Still, not a bad idea.